<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News &#8211; Apac jp cc prod wrapper</title>
	<atom:link href="https://apac-jp-cc-prod-wrapper.amway.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://apac-jp-cc-prod-wrapper.amway.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 07:05:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>2023 Beer &#038; Brewer Awards winners</title>
		<link>https://apac-jp-cc-prod-wrapper.amway.com/2023-beer-brewer-awards-winners/</link>
					<comments>https://apac-jp-cc-prod-wrapper.amway.com/2023-beer-brewer-awards-winners/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 07:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://apac-jp-cc-prod-wrapper.amway.com/?p=19</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Despite the beer world spending much of this year feeling like it’s dealing in powder kegs rather than the ones we’re more accustomed to such has been the minefield of obstacles to navigate, there will always be room, and indeed the need, to celebrate the wins. So as the Beer &#38; Brewer Awards return for another year ... <a title="2023 Beer &#038; Brewer Awards winners" class="read-more" href="https://apac-jp-cc-prod-wrapper.amway.com/2023-beer-brewer-awards-winners/" aria-label="More on 2023 Beer &#038; Brewer Awards winners">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Despite the beer world spending much of this year feeling like it’s dealing in powder kegs rather than the ones we’re more accustomed to such has been the minefield of obstacles to navigate, there will always be room, and indeed the need, to celebrate the wins.</strong></p>
<p>So as the <em>Beer &amp; Brewer</em> Awards return for another year it’s timelier than ever to be shining a spotlight on some of those who have raised the bar and given us all plenty of reasons to raise a toast.</p>
<p>From a lifetime of achievement to a new brewing company that’s spent the last 12 months high achieving, our winners highlight what is great and healthy about the broader industry at a time when it needs all the limelight it can get.</p>
<p>Like last year, votes from our panel of judges (see below for the full list) were counted alongside ones from the public who gave their opinions via an online poll on our website back in September. It meant that the counting process was long and whilst some categories were largely a one-horse race, some were tightly contested which goes to show the level of competition, and passion, evident in the industry across the country.</p>
<p>Congratulations to all our winners but the biggest toast must go to everyone in the industry who continue to strive for excellence and who celebrate our vibrant beer culture.</p>
<p><em><strong>These awards feature in the summer 2023/24 edition of Beer &amp; Brewer that is officially available from December 1. Head </strong><strong>here</strong><strong> to discover all of our great subscription offers.</strong></em></p>
<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>The 2023<em> Beer &amp; Brewer </em>Awards winners</strong></h4>
<p><strong>Lifetime Achievement:</strong><br />
<strong>Tina Panoutsos</strong><br />
From her support of the entire beer category, including from a sensory education and evaluation point of view as one of the world’s best palates right through to her mentorship and care for a growing legion of women in the industry, Tina is held in the very highest regard and is the embodiment of what it means to win a lifetime achievement award. <strong>Read our awards feature on Tina here.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Brewer of the Year: Matt Wilson, Moffat Beach Brewing</strong><br />
After repeat high achievement on the awards circuit for the past five years, Matt has steered Moffat Beach from very humble beginnings to the success story they now are, whilst keeping this family-run brewery’s feet still very much firmly on the ground.<br />
<strong>Read our awards feature on Matt here.</strong></p>
<p><strong>New Brewing Company of the Year: Du Cane Brewing</strong><br />
Much like the mountain range they’re named after, Launceston’s Du Cane Brewing is a major tourist destination in a region renowned for them whilst concurrently being something that represents the local community right down to a tee.<br />
<strong>Read our awards feature on Du Cane here.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Beer Venue of the Year:</strong><br />
<strong>The Grain Store</strong><br />
In their tenth year of operation, this Newcastle craft beer institution is the long overdue winner of this award and the first regional venue to do so. Always wholly and fiercely independent, The Grain Store is a spiritual home for Australian indie craft that backs it unconditionally at a time it needs all the backing it can get. <strong>Read our awards feature on The Grain Store here.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Brewpub of the Year:</strong><br />
<strong>Felons Brewing Co</strong><br />
In five years, Felons have gone from famously running out of beer in their opening few weeks to being an integral part of the cultural fabric of their home city. With an enviable and large location on Brisbane River, they are many things to many people, and are invariably busy. But their hospitality remains customer-focussed and their range of beer styles are always excellent.<br />
<strong>Read our awards feature on Felons here.</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://apac-jp-cc-prod-wrapper.amway.com/2023-beer-brewer-awards-winners/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Burleigh Brewing reposition their brand</title>
		<link>https://apac-jp-cc-prod-wrapper.amway.com/burleigh-brewing-reposition-their-brand/</link>
					<comments>https://apac-jp-cc-prod-wrapper.amway.com/burleigh-brewing-reposition-their-brand/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 07:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://apac-jp-cc-prod-wrapper.amway.com/?p=15</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Burleigh Brewing have introduced three new lagers to their core range and a new-look as they seek to highlight a “slow brewed” approach to their beers. As well as new designs across their range, Burleigh’s brand reposition sees them add a mid-strength version of their pioneering Bighead zero carb lager – the Bighead Mid (3% ... <a title="Burleigh Brewing reposition their brand" class="read-more" href="https://apac-jp-cc-prod-wrapper.amway.com/burleigh-brewing-reposition-their-brand/" aria-label="More on Burleigh Brewing reposition their brand">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Burleigh Brewing have introduced three new lagers to their core range and a new-look as they seek to highlight a “slow brewed” approach to their beers.</strong></p>
<p>As well as new designs across their range, Burleigh’s brand reposition sees them add a mid-strength version of their pioneering Bighead zero carb lager – the Bighead Mid (3% ABV) – as well as 4.2% and 3% versions of the Slow Brewed Lager.</p>
<p>CEO Peta Fielding, who founded the brewery on the Gold Coast with husband and master brewer Brennan in 2006, said in a statement the changes were an “evolution of the brand’s premium positioning”.</p>
<p>“We’ve re-positioned our brand to shine a light on our slow brewing ethos.” Peta said. “We like to take our time to do things right, and to us, beer done right means extra time in the tanks.</p>
<p>“Only the natural passing of time ferments and ages our beer. No shit, no shortcuts!”</p>
<p>Burleigh said all three new lagers are available in 330ml bottles, 375ml cans and 50L kegs.</p>
<p>New packaging has been rolled out with the launch of the lagers this month while Burleigh’s range of ales will follow suit early in 2024.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://apac-jp-cc-prod-wrapper.amway.com/burleigh-brewing-reposition-their-brand/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hazy pale ale collab celebrates women in beer</title>
		<link>https://apac-jp-cc-prod-wrapper.amway.com/hazy-pale-ale-collab-celebrates-women-in-beer/</link>
					<comments>https://apac-jp-cc-prod-wrapper.amway.com/hazy-pale-ale-collab-celebrates-women-in-beer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 07:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://apac-jp-cc-prod-wrapper.amway.com/?p=13</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bottleshop Blackhearts &#38; Sparrows has teamed up with the Pink Boots Society of Australia and Sydney’s Philter Brewing on the limited release hazy pale ale Juicy that’s been brewed to drive awareness and raise funds for empowering women in the beer industry. With $18 from every case and $3 from each four-pack sold going directly ... <a title="Hazy pale ale collab celebrates women in beer" class="read-more" href="https://apac-jp-cc-prod-wrapper.amway.com/hazy-pale-ale-collab-celebrates-women-in-beer/" aria-label="More on Hazy pale ale collab celebrates women in beer">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Bottleshop Blackhearts &amp; Sparrows has teamed up with the Pink Boots Society of Australia and Sydney’s Philter Brewing on the limited release hazy pale ale Juicy that’s been brewed to drive awareness and raise funds for empowering women in the beer industry.</strong></p>
<p>With $18 from every case and $3 from each four-pack sold going directly to the Pink Boots Society of Australia, Juicy’s brew day saw Blackhearts &amp; Sparrows’ beer buyer Cherry Murphy join Pink Boots’ NSW members at Philter’s Marrickville brewery (pictured above).</p>
<p>Sitting right at the heart of the beer is Yakima Chief Hops’ Pink Boots 2022 hop blend, made up of Loral, Eukanot and HBC 586 hops. Mosaic and Citra were also added with just a touch of Sabro.</p>
<p>The limited-edition Juicy is available exclusively through Blackhearts &amp; Sparrows stores and is available for purchase across Victoria, Canberra, Hobart and online.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://apac-jp-cc-prod-wrapper.amway.com/hazy-pale-ale-collab-celebrates-women-in-beer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
